JANE AKUNMA AMUNEKE

+2348036709144 jane.akunma@gmail.com Registry Unit Rivers State University Nkpolu, Oroworukwo Port Harcourt Rivers State, Nigeria

SUMMARY

I am a seasoned administrator with over 11 years of banking experience, and various administrative roles in the Rivers State University Port Harcourt Rivers State Nigeria. Possessing strong work ethics, superb initiatives, good decision making skills, as well as an excellent time manager with good communication skills.

I am a native English Speaker with distinguished levels in IELTS General (Speaking 7.5, Writing 7.0, Reading 6.0 and Listening 6.0) Overall band of 6.5 **RESEARCH INTERESTS**

Organizational Behavior- Conflict and Negotiations, Leadership, decision making and Performance.

Strategic Management- Innovation and entrepreneurship, Organizational learning and change, Risk taking and risk management

Information Systems- Digital capabilities in modern organisations, Digital innovation and organisational transformation, Sustainability, climate change and digital resilience, emerging technologies.

Human resource management- Career development, Job analysis and design, organizational socialization, Entrepreneurship.

Public Administration and Bureaucracy, Administrative Reforms due to bureaucracy.

EDUCATION

MSc Rivers State University Port Harcourt, Nigeria 2022

April

Human Resource Management

MBA Ladoke Akintola University of Technology Ogbomosho 2018

May

Osun State Nigeria.

Financial Management

B.Tech Federal University of Technology Owerri Imo state, Nigeria May 2005

Industrial Microbiology

WORK EXPERIENCE

Department of Medical Biochemistry College of Medical Sciences Rivers State University Port Harcourt Administrative Officer April 2023 – Date

To serve as the primary point of administrative contact and liaison with other offices, individuals, and institutions on operational matters concerning the department.

To take down and develop minutes of meetings, and ensure that they are is recorded accurately and that actions are communicated, addressed, monitored and reported back to future meetings.

To assists in the coordination, supervision, and completion of special projects, in the department when requested by the Head of Department

To assist the Head of Department in aspects of budgets and resource management (monitor expenditures) for the department.

To provide assistance in the understanding and interpretation of University policies and procedures, as appropriate, and ensure that office operations are in compliance with policy provisions and standards.

Department of Exams and Records. October 2019 –April 2023 Rivers State University Port Harcourt. Nigeria

ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICER:

- Preparation of Minutes of Meeting for Assessment and Grade Requirements Committee of Senate Rivers State University Port Harcourt (A&GRC).
- Preparation of Student's Transcripts, including dispatch.
- Attendance and Representation of the Exams and Records Unit at Senate Meetings.
- Coordinate, Review and investigate Complaints around Transcript Request and Track Delivery.
- Ensure collation of Treated Transcript Request to Directors for Authentication and Approvals.

First City Monument Bank Ltd, 2007 - 2019

HEAD OF OPERATIONS / VAULT CUSTODIAN / CUSTOMER SERVICE

Manage and Coordinate all cash activities in the Banking hall.

Approve ATM Request for Customers and PIN selection

Coordinate and Supervise activities of Tellers, Head tellers and Customer Service Officers.

Verify and approve cash and Cheque postings to all accounts.

Supervise and oversee ATM machine uptime and adequate upload of cash.

Request cash and monitor Vault activities.

Reconciliation of ATM and all Internal Accounts.

Approve account Opening Request from Customer Service Officer

NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS (NYSC)

National Agency for Food Administration and control (NAFDAC) Kano Zone Enforcement, Raids and collation of Drugs, Beverages Drinks or Analysis.

LANGUAGES

English: Native Language, Distinguished levels in Listening, Speaking, Reading, and Writing

OTHER SKILLS AND COMPETENCES

Microsoft Packages: Distinguished level of proficiency